

shaktimankushwaha14@gmail.com

+917746058714

O Pune

Pune, Maharashtra.

Shaktiman Kushwaha

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

Higher Secondary: 2016-2018

MLB Higher Secondary School Singrauli MP Scored 80% with PCM

Bachelor Of Technology

Shri Ram Institute of Technology Jabalpur Mechanical Engineering with 7.5 CGPA

SKILLS

Java

Spring boot

React JS

MySQL

JavaScript

Angular

React Native

REFERENCES

GitHub

<u>LeetCode</u>

LinkedIN

Address

Phone: +91774605874

Perfect PG2, Mukai Nagar, Hinjewadi Pune,

Maharashtra.

PROFILE

Leveraging 1.7+ years of full stack expertise, I've driven innovation and delivered solutions for projects valued at over \$1 million. I excel in collaborative team settings, working effectively with 10+ members. As an aspiring Software Development Engineer, I'm committed to continuous learning and growth, having enhanced project efficiency by 30%. Dedicated to contributing to forward-thinking projects, I aim to create a meaningful impact in technology.

EXPERIENCE

Infosys Limited

June 2023-Present

System Engineer

- Led software development using Spring Boot and React JS, crafting scalable microservices and interfaces.
- Integrated frontend with backend microservices, optimizing system performance and ensuring seamless operation.
- Implemented secure RESTful APIs, bolstering data exchange reliability, system security, and user trust.
- Collaborated in agile teams, fostering innovation, efficiency, and effective communication for top-notch solutions.

Infosys Limited

Dec 2022- June 2023

System Engineer Trainee

- 3 Months of training at infosys Limited in backend technologies Like Java, Spring Boot , Node JS, Express JS.
- 3 Months of training in Infosys Limited in frontend React JS, HTML, CSS, BootStrap, SCSS, tailwind CSS.
- 1 month of additional training of Spring Microservices.

Projects

HolaChats

- A chatting application build and deployed on Netlify by me from scratch where, as a user i can register myself to the application and login to the site.
- I can also search for the another registered user to the application and chat with them live and can also share the images, all the chats and the shared data is end to end protected.

TECHNOLOGY USED: JavaScript, React JS, HTML, SCSS, Google Firebase, Netlify, github, git.